Guide to the Student Government Association Records RG 5.15
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series 11: Raymond Lubus-SGA President (1978-80), 41507
  - Series 26: Justin Molito-SGA President (1994-95), 41151
    - Constitutional Revision Committee, 1994, 1994-1995; 41167 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Public Safety, 1994-1995; 41166 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Off Campus Housing Report, 1995, 1994-1995; 41165 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Guest Speakers, 1994-1995; 41164 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - WCSU Economic Impact Analysis, April 95, 1994-1995; 41163 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - WCSU Dept. By-Laws, 1994-1995; 41162 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - University Senate Min., April 94-May 95, 1994-1995; 41161 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Student Center Board Constitution, 1994-1995; 41160 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - V.M.O.J.A. Constitution, 1994-1995; 41159 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Roots & Shoots Constitution, 1994-1995; 41158 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Fee Breakdown at All CSU Schools, 1994, 1994-1995; 41157 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - 1994-96 Club & Organization Fact Sheets, 1994-1995; 41156 (Box 12, Folder 38-41)
    - 1994-96 Board of Trustees Min., May 94-Jan 96, 1994-1995; 41155 (Box 12, Folder 42-43)
    - 1994-99 SGA Clubs & Organization Lists, 1994-1995; 41154 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - 1994-99 Board of Trustees Min, 1994-1995; 41153 (Box 12, Folder 45-47)
    - 1994-2000 SGA Roll Call & Voting Records, Aug 94-Jan 00, 1994-1995; 41152 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Series 12: Anthony Saviano-SGA President (1980-81), 41479
  - SGA Min., May 80-April 81, 1980-1981; 41506 (Box 4, Folder 51-53)
  - Budget Hearings, 1981, 1980-1981; 41505 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Budget Requests, 1980-1981; 41504 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Financial Reports, 1980-1981; 41503 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Impeachment of John Lenord, 1981, 1980-1981; 41502 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Campus Info, 1980-1981; 41501 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Forms & Commuter Student Survey, 1980-1981; 41500 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Student Union Room Reservations, May 80-May 81, 1980-1981; 41499 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Letter from Stage Presence, 1981, 1980-1981; 41498 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - WCSC Staff Bulletin, Aug 80- May-81, 1980-1981; 41497 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - List of all full-time undergrads, 1980-1981; 41496 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Notes to President Saviano, 1980-1981; 41495 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Student Advisory Board Proposed Constitution, 1980, 1980-1981; 41494 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Board of Trustees Min., Sept-Nov 80, 1980-1981; 41493 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Election Resolution, 1975, 1980-1981; 41492 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Invitation to Spring Festival, 1981, 1980-1981; 41491 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - WCSC Faculty in Focus, Dec 79- Mar-81, 1980-1981; 41490 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - SAGA Contract (food service), 1976, 1980-1981; 41489 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Colleges & Universities: Reports, May-Aug 80, 1980-1981; 41488 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Colleges & Universities: Newsletters, July-Nov 80, 1980-1981; 41487 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - American Student Association, 1980, 1980-1981; 41486 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - United States Student Association, May 80-March 81, 1980-1981; 41485 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Collegiate Headlines, Feb 80- Apr-81, 1980-1981; 41484 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Intercollegiate Press Bulletins, Sept 80-May 81, 1980-1981; 41483 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - National On Campus Report, Aug 79-April 81, 1980-1981; 41482 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - N.S.E.F Cognition, 1980-1981; 41481 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Office of Education: The Bulletin, Nov 79-Feb 81, 1980-1981; 41480 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Series 13: Joni Gomes-SGA President (1981-82), 41464
  - SGA Min., May 81-April 82, 1981-1982; 41478 (Box 5, Folder 15-17)
  - SGA E-Board Min., 1981-82, 1981-1982; 41477 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - WCSC Budget, 1981-83, 1981-1982; 41476 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - WCSC Budget Process, 1981-83, 1981-1982; 41475 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Committee Reports, 1981-82, 1981-1982; 41474 (Box 5, Folder 21-23)
  - Homecoming, Fall 81, 1981-1982; 41473 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Information Center, 1981-82, 1981-1982; 41472 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - University Recreational Committee, 1983, 1981-1982; 41471 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Yearbook, 1981-82, 1981-1982; 41470 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Blue Ribbon Commission, Jan-March 82, 1981-1982; 41469 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Search Committee: VP of Academic Affairs, 1982, 1981-1982; 41468 (Box 5, Folder 29-30)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1981-1983; 41467 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Budget & Tuition Fees, 1981-1984; 41466 (Box 5, Folder 32-33)
  - Club Constitutions, 1981-1987; 41465 (Box 5, Folder 34-36)
- Series 14: Mark Block-SGA President (1982-83), 41391
  - SGA Min., May 82-May 83, 1982-1983; 41463 (Box 5, Folder 37-39)
  - Budget Requests & Min., 1982-83 Budget Requests & Min., 1982-83, 1982-1983; 41462 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Block: SGA Elections, 1979-82, 1982-1983; 41461 (Box 5, Folder 41-42)
  - Memos to SGA Senators, April 82- Apr-83, 1982-1983; 41460 (Box 5, Folder 43-44)
  - University Senate Min., April 82- Apr-83, 1982-1983; 41459 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - WCSC Commencement Program, May 16 1982, 1982-1983; 41458 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - WCSC Honors Convention: Ives Concert Hall, May 1982, 1982-1983; 41457 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Clubs Carnival, 1982, 1982-1983; 41456 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - College Union Intern, 1982, 1982-1983; 41455 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Student Advisory Board, Oct 82, 1982-1983; 41454 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Student Life, 1982-83, 1982-1983; 41453 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Residence Hall Policy, 1982, 1982-1983; 41452 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Career Development Center, 1982-83, 1982-1983; 41451 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Reaccredidation, Feb 82-March 83, 1982-1983; 41450 (Box 5, Folder 54-55)
  - Student Life Committee, Feb 82- Mar-83, 1982-1983; 41449 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Haas/Alumni Association Awards, 1983, 1982-1983; 41448 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Full-time Undergrads, Fall 82, 1982-1983; 41447 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Information Sheets, 1983, 1982-1983; 41446 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - WCSC Staff Bulletin & WCSU Staff Bulletin, May 82-May 83, 1982-1983; 41445 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NEASC Committee, 1982, 1982-1983; 41444 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondences, 1982-83, 1982-1983; 41443 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondences (Block), 1982-83, 1982-1983; 41442 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Outside Mail to SGA, 1982-83, 1982-1983; 41441 (Box 6, Folder 9-11)
  - Class of 83: 1979-80, 1982-1983; 41440 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Class of 83: Fall 80, 1982-1983; 41439 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Class of 83: Spring 81, 1982-1983; 41438 (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
  - Class of 83: Financial Records, 1980-81, 1982-1983; 41437 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Class of 83: Correspondence, 1980-81, 1982-1983; 41436 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Class of 83: Personal, 1980-81, 1982-1983; 41435 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Legal Drinking Issue, 1982, 1982-1983; 41434 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - WCSC Student Handbook, 1981, 1982-1983; 41433 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Ancell School of Business Annual Reports, 1980-81, 1982-1983; 41432 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 1982 Yearbook Plans, 1981 1982 Yearbook Plans, 1981, 1982-1983; 41431 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Taylor Publishing Material (Yearbook), 1981-82, 1982-1983; 41430 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Dept. of Education, May-82-Jan 83, 1982-1983; 41429 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Architectural Accessibility for Disabled, 1976, 1982-1983; 41428 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Muscular Dystrophy Association, 1980, 1982-1983; 41427 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - A.S.A: National Student Convention, Washington, DC, 1981, 1982-1983; 41426 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - A.S.A: National Student Convention, Washington, DC, 1982, 1982-1983; 41425 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - A.S.A: Boston Convention, 1982, 1982-1983; 41424 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - A.S.A: Misc., 1982-83, 1982-1983; 41423 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - U.S. Student Association, 1983, 1982-1983; 41422 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Collegiate Headlines, April 82- Jul-83, 1982- 1983; 41421 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Collegiate Headlines, April 82- Jul-83, 1982-1983; 41420 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Intercollegiate Press Bulletins, April 82-May 83, 1982-1983; 41419 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - National On-Campus Report, June 82-April 83, 1982-1983; 41418 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Student Press Services (newspaper), Sept-82-April 83, 1982-1983; 41417 (Box 6, Folder 35-36)
  - National Coalition of Graduate Student Associations, 1982, 1982-1983; 41416 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Atlantic City information, 1981, 1982-1983; 41415 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Superdance USA, 1982-83, 1982-1983; 41414 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - History of Western CT State College: 75 Years, 1903-1978, 1978, 1982-1983; 41413 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - A.Z.A Membership (Block), 1978-79, 1982-1983; 41412 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - A.Z.A Life Membership (Block), 1982-83, 1982-1983; 41411 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Org.: International Districts, 1976-79, 1982-1983; 41410 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Org.: District 1-22, 1978-79, 1982-1983; 41409 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Org.: Memorandums, 1978-79, 1982-1983; 41408 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Org.: Newsletters, 1978-79, 1982-1983; 41407 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Org.: Conventions & Overnights, 1978-81, 1982-1983; 41406 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Org.: Basketball/Volleyball League, 1979, 1982-1983; 41405 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Org.: General Misc., 1977-80, 1982-1983; 41404 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Org.: Misc. Policies, 1977, 1982-1983; 41403 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Org.: CT Valley Region I notes, 1978-79, 1982-1983; 41402 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Org.: CT Valley Region I Kohome Godol, 1978-80, 1982-1983; 41401 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Org.: CT Valley Region I Alumni Assoc., 1980-83, 1982-1983; 41400 (Box 6, Folder 53-54)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Org.: Elath A.Z.A, 1977-78, 1982-1983; 41399 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - SGA Folder, 1983, 1982-1983; 41398 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Medalic Sculpture Pamphlet, 1976, 1982-1983; 41397 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Rotaract Pamphlet, 1982, 1982-1983; 41396 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Personal Misc. (Block), 1978-80, 1982-1983; 41395 (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
  - Misc. notes, 1982-83, 1982-1983; 41394 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Misc., 1982-83, 1982-1983; 41393 (Box 7, Folder 7-9)
  - Correspondences, May 82-Nov 85, 1982-1985; 41392 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Series 15: Linda Adley-SGA President (1983-84), 41360
  - SGA Min., Sept 83-April 84, 1983-1984; 41390 (Box 7, Folder 11-13)
  - SGA E-Board Min., Sept 83, 1983-1984; 41389 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - SGA Senators & schedules, 1983-84, 1983-1984; 41388 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Budget Requests, 1983-84, 1983-1984; 41387 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Club Budget Requests, 1983-84, 1983-1984; 41386 (Box 7, Folder 17-18)
  - Club Information, 1983-84, 1983-1984; 41385 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Correspondences, 1983-84, 1983-1984; 41384 (Box 7, Folder 20-21)
  - Correspondences to Adley, 1983-84, 1983-1984; 41383 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Outside Mail & Promotions to SGA, 1983-84, 1983-1984; 41382 (Box 7, Folder 23-24)
  - Student Life, 1983-84, 1983-1984; 41381 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Student Advisory Board, Sept 83- Apr 84, 1983-1984; 41380 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Orientation, Fall 83, 1983-1984; 41379 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Fall Week, 1983, 1983-1984; 41378 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Site Committee for Art Work: Grasso Hall, May-June 83, 1983-1984; 41377 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Commission on the Arts, 1983-84, 1983-1984; 41376 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Board of Trustees, May 83-April 84, 1983-1984; 41375 (Box 7, Folder 31-32)
  - News Releases, 1983-84, 1983-1984; 41374 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - WCSU Staff Bulletin, Aug 83- May 84, 1983-1984; 41373 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - A.S.A: National Student Conference, Washington DC, July 1982, 1983-1984; 41372 (Box 7, Folder 35-36)
  - American Student Association, 1982-83, 1983-1984; 41371 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Education Update (Dept. of Ed.), Spring 83-March 84, 1983-1984; 41370 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Intercollegiate Press Bulletins, Sept 83- April 84, 1983-1984; 41369 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - National On-Campus Report, May 83-April 84, 1983-1984; 41368 (Box 7, Folder 40-41)
  - Student Press Services, May 83- Apr 84, 1983-1984; 41367 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - United Way campaign, 1983, 1983-1984; 41366 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Olympic Regional Development Authority: Lake Placid, NY, 1983-84, 1983-1984; 41365 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Misc., 1982-83, 1983-1984; 41364 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - 1983-86 Correspondences, 1983-1984; 41363 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - 1983-87 WCSU Folder & Bumpersticker, 1983-1984; 41362 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - 1983-92 Misc. SGA Min. & Budgets, 1983-1984; 41361 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Series 16: Peter Retalis-SGA President (1984-85), 41354
  - SGA Min., Sept 84-April 85, 1983-1984; 41359 (Box 7, Folder 49-50)
  - Budget Requests, 1984-85, 1983-1984; 41358 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Misc., 1984-85, 1983-1984; 41357 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - 1984-89 Student Activity Fund: Trial Balance Sheets, 1983-1984; 41356 (Box 7, Folder 53-54)
  - 1984-91 WCSU Student Handbooks: 1984-85, 1983-1991; 41355 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Series 17: John Gill-SGA President (1985-86), 41344
  - SGA Min., May 85-May 86, 1985-1986; 41353 (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
  - Budget Requests, 1985-1986; 41352 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - University Wide Committees, 1985-1986; 41351 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dean of Student Affairs Search Committee, 1985, 1985-1986; 41350 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Freedom of Information, 1985, 1985-1986; 41349 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Student Advisory Board, Sept 85- Mar 86, 1985-1986; 41348 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Misc., 1985-1986; 41347 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1985-87 CT Student Association, 1985-1986; 41346 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 1985-90 Misc. information, 1985-1986; 41345 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Series 18: Louis Alhage-SGA President (1986-87), 41314
  - SGA Min., April 86-April 87, 1986-1987; 41343 (Box 8, Folder 13-14)
  - SGA Min. w/ notes, Feb 87, 1986-1987; 41342 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - SGA Members, 1986-1987; 41341 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Budget Requests, 1986-1987; 41340 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Budget Hearings, 1986-1987; 41339 (Box 8, Folder 19-21)
  - Budget Hearings w/notes, 1986-1987; 41338 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Balance Sheets, July 86-June 87, 1986-1987; 41337 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Student Activity Fund, 1986-1987; 41336 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Budgets, 1986-1987; 41335 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - SGA Clubs, 1986-1987; 41334 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Correspondences, 1986-1987; 41333 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - SGA Constitution, 1986-1987; 41332 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Student Advisory Board Min., Oct 86-May 87, 1986-1987; 41331 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - University Planning Committee, 1986-1987; 41330 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Student Life Committee, 1986-1987; 41329 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Child Care Program, 1986, 1986-1987; 41328 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Bookstore Committee, 1986, 1986-1987; 41327 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Legislative Task Force, 1986, 1986-1987; 41326 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Governor's Student Financial Aid Task Force, 1986-1987; 41325 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - University Senate Min., May 86-April 87, 1986-1987; 41324 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - University Recreational Association Committee Report, Sept-Nov 86, 1986-1987; 41323 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - New Student Orientation, 1986, 1986-1987; 41322 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - DAKA (food service), 1986-1987; 41321 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - CSU 5th Year Celebration, 1987, 1986-1987; 41320 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - WCSU Staff Bulletin, Sept 86- Apr 87, 1986-1987; 41319 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - U.S. National Student Association, Sept 86-April 87, 1986-1987; 41318 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - SGA misc., 1986, 1986-1987; 41317 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - 1986-89 Misc., 1986-1987; 41316 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - 1986-90 Club Fact Sheets, 1986-1987; 41315 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Series 19: Janine Brentari-SGA President (1987-88), 41277
  - SGA Min., May 87-May 88, 1987-1988; 41313 (Box 8, Folder 46-49)
  - SGA Min. w/notes, Sept 87-Oct 88, 1987-1988; 41312 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - SGA Senators, Officers, & the Class of 87, 1987-1988; 41311 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Budget Hearings/Requests, 1987-1988; 41310 (Box 8, Folder 52-53)
  - Budgets Budgets, 1987-1988; 41309 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Club Budget Requests, 1987-1988; 41308 (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
  - SGA Clubs, 1987-1988; 41307 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondences, March-Nov 87, 1987-1988; 41306 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondences, 1987-1988; 41305 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondences w/ Dr. Richard Sullivan, Oct 87, 1987-1988; 41304 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Balance Sheets, Aug 87-May 88, 1987-1988; 41303 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Search Committees, 1987-1988; 41302 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Associate Dean Search Committee, 1987, 1987-1988; 41301 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Library, 1987-1988; 41300 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Homecoming, 1987, 1987-1988; 41299 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Programs & Activities, 1987, 1987-1988; 41298 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - University Senate Min., Sept 87- Apr 88, 1987-1988; 41297 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - University Planning Committee, April-Oct 87, 1987-1988; 41296 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - WCSU Staff Bulletin, Sept 87-Feb 88, 1987-1988; 41295 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - NEASC Steering Committee, 1987, 1987-1988; 41294 (Box 9, Folder 18-20)
  - SGA Questionnaire, Spring 88, 1987-1988; 41293 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - SGA Survey: "3 Biggest Issues at WCSU," April 88, 1987-1988; 41292 (Box 9, Folder 22-27)
  - Board of Governors for Higher Education, 1987-1988; 41291 (Box 9, Folder 28-31)
  - New England Association of Schools, 1987-1988; 41290 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Day Student Government, 1987-1988; 41289 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - The Echo, Sept-Nov 87, 1987-1988; 41288 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - CSU Material, 1987, 1987-1988; 41287 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - United Way campaign, 1987, 1987- 1988; 41286 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Macy's Promotional Material, 1987, 1987-1988; 41285 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Power at Your Fingertips: Resource Manual (CCSU), 1988, 1987-1988; 41284 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - The Leading Edge: Action Resource Manual (CCSU), 1987-1988; 41283 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Misc. notes, 1987-1988; 41282 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - SGA misc., 1987-1988; 41281 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - 1987-89 CT Inc.: Financial Statement & Schedules, 1987-1988; 41280 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - 1987-92 Student Activities Fund Handbooks; 1991-92, 1987-1988; 41279 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - 1987-95 Budget Committee & Student Activity Fund, 1987-1988; 41278 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Series 20: Kristina Testa-SGA President (1988-89), 41237
  - SGA Min., April 88-April 89, 1988-1989; 41276 (Box 9, Folder 45-49)
  - SGA E-Board Min., 1988-1989; 41275 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - SGA Officers & Senators, 1988-1989; 41274 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Budget Requests, 1988-1989; 41273 (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
  - Balance Sheets, Aug 88-May 89, 1988-1989; 41272 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Financial Reports, 1988-1989; 41271 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - SGA Finance Board Min., 1989, 1988-1989; 41270 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondences, April 88-Dec 89, 1988-1989; 41269 (Box 10, Folder 7-9)
  - SGA Constitution (drafts), 1974-89, 1988-1989; 41268 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Student Activity Fund Handbook, 1988-1989; 41267 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Homecoming, 1988, 1988-1989; 41266 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Open House, 1988, 1988-1989; 41265 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Dance Marathon, 1989, 1988-1989; 41264 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Housing, 1988-1989; 41263 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Dean Muska, 1988, 1988-1989; 41262 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - WCSU Staff Bulletin, Aug 88- Apr 89, 1988-1989; 41261 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - University Recreational Policy Association, 1988-1989; 41260 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Intramurals & Recreational Manual, 1988-1989; 41259 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Recreation Situation, 1988-1989; 41258 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Academic Council, 1988-1989; 41257 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Investigation Committee Report, 1988, 1988-1989; 41256 (Box 10, Folder 22-23)
  - Investigation Committee Report, 1989, 1988-1989; 41255 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - University Senate Min., Sept 88- Feb 89, 1988-1989; 41254 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Board of Trustees, 1988, 1988-1989; 41253 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Course Cancellation Committee, 1988-1989; 41252 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - NEASC Steering Committee, 1988, 1988-1989; 41251 (Box 10, Folder 28-29)
  - Step-Up WCSU: A Summer Evaluation Program, Nov 88, 1988-1989; 41250 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Fifth Year Report (draft), April 88, 1988-1989; 41249 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Minority Student Enrollment Survey, 1988, 1988-1989; 41248 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Library Hours Survey, 1989, 1988-1989; 41247 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1988, 1988-1989; 41246 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - CT Student Association, 1988-1989; 41245 (Box 10, Folder 35-36)
  - Education Updates, 1988-1989; 41244 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - National On-Campus Report, July 88-April 89, 1988-1989; 41243 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Higher Education Operating Budget Request, 1988, 1988-1989; 41242 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Conferences, 1988-1989; 41241 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Da Anza College (California) information, 1988-1989; 41240 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - SGA Misc., 1988-1989; 41239 (Box 10, Folder 42-43)
  - Misc., 1988-1989; 41238 (Box 10, Folder 44-45)
- Series 21: Susy Snearly-SGA President (1989-90), 41210
  - SGA Min., Sept 89-April 90, 1989-1990; 41236 (Box 10, Folder 46-47)
  - SGA Elections, 1989-1990; 41235 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - SGA Members, 1989-1990; 41234 (Box 10, Folder 49-50)
  - Budget Requests, 1989-1990; 41233 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - Financial Reports, 1989-1990; 41232 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - SGA Constitution & By-Laws, 1989-1990; 41231 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondences, March 89-April 90, 1989- 1990; 41230 (Box 11, Folder 5-7)
  - Basic Studies Program, 1989-1990; 41229 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Homecoming, 1989, 1989-1990; 41228 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Admissions Committee, Sept 89- Apr 90, 1989-1990; 41227 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Board of Governors, 1989-1990; 41226 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - University Senate, 1989-1990; 41225 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - University Committees, 1989-1990; 41224 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Student Advisory Board, 1989-1990; 41223 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Student Advisory Board Min., Dec 89-Dec 90, 1989-1990; 41222 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees, April 89-Jan 91, 1989-1990; 41221 (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
  - Course Cancellation Committee, 1989-1990; 41220 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Graduate Studies Committee, 1989, 1989-1990; 41219 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Graduate School Fair, 1990, 1989-1990; 41218 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Annual Reports, 1989-1990; 41217 (Box 11, Folder 21-22)
  - Vision Statement, 1989, 1989-1990; 41216 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - CSU Budget Issue, 1989-1990; 41215 (Box 11, Folder 24-25)
  - NEASC Report, 1989-1990; 41214 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - University Foundation of Western CT Inc., 1989-1990; 41213 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - U.S. Student Association, 1989-1990; 41212 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Misc., 1989-1990; 41211 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Series 22: Robert Trotta-SGA President (1990-91), 41201
  - SGA Min., May 90-May 91, 1990-1991; 41209 (Box 11, Folder 30-32)
  - SGA Min (notebook), Jan-May 91, 1990-1991; 41208 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - SGA Members, 1990-1991; 41207 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; 41206 (Box 11, Folder 35-36)
  - Budget Requests, 1990-1991; 41205 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Misc., 1990-1991; 41204 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - 1990-92 SGA Elections & Awards, 1990-1991; 41203 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - 1990-94 SGA notes, 1990-1991; 41202 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Series 23: Ursula Gleissner-SGA President (1991-92), 41195
  - SGA Min., Sept 91-May 92, 1991-1992; 41200 (Box 11, Folder 41-42)
  - SGA Min. (notebook), Sept 91- Mar 92, 1991-1992; 41199 (Box 11, Folder 43)